

KONTAK

- +6285230010042
- loeby45@gmail.com
- apitoong.com
- apitoong
- afitra
- Bē afitramamor
- in afitra mamor

SKILLS

- Swift
- Git
- NodeJs
- Linux
- Golang
- Mysql
- VueJs
- Postgre
- NuxtJs
- MongoDB
- ExpressJs
- Laravel

AFITRA MAMOR B. SOFTWARE ENGINEER

As a software developer with less than 5 years of experience, I have proven capable of working as a backend and frontend web developer. In the midst of my busy life as a software developer, I also run a business in the field of selling agricultural products, namely buying and selling orange leaves. Based on the experience I have, I can help companies that will accept me both technically and ideas

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2020

Apple Developer Academy

- Learn to use CBL as as application development framework
- Make application development plans and act as project menejement
- Prepare for product backlog items based on user stories
- conduct research and find out about the difficulities and need of the user to be implemented into an application



KONTAK

- +6285230010042
- loeby45@gmail.com
- apitoong.com

PENDIDIKAN

2018

HACKTIV8

student phase 2 full stack developer

2014-2019

UNIVERSITAS HASYIM ASY ARY

D3 Menejemen Informatika

2011-2018

TEBUIRENG ISLAMIC BOARDING SCHOOL

Senior High School | Santri

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2020

Apple Developer Academy

- developed the app using swift
- implement the application view of the design that has been provide

2018 - 2019

Digital one | Full stack Developer

- Implement architectural microservices as a framework
- Do the main application development, application for marketing and sales
- The task distribution system using asana and takes the sprint backlog that is available when task is complete
- The frontend framework used
 Vuejs, while the backend uses the
 laravel framework
- I also had several turns working on the application for client event which were done at latest 2 times every month
- Accustomed to working on the client requests suddenly



KONTAK

- +6285230010042
- loeby45@gmail.com
- apitoong.com

PENDIDIKAN

2018

HACKTIV8

student phase 2 full stack developer

2014-2019

UNIVERSITAS HASYIM ASY ARY

D3 Menejemen Informatika

2011-2018

 TEBUIRENG ISLAMIC BOARDING SCHOOL

Senior High School | Santri

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - now

Freelance Programmer

- Build frontend and backend in web and android application development
- Deploy to server / hosting

Project

- http://mambaulhikam.org
- https://tigadewitimurraya.com
- https://apitoong.com
- https://ukaisya.com/
- http://beli.apitoong.com
- https://www.behance.net/gallery/1
 08307117/Soulam-Embroidery Digital-Painting-App
- https://www.behance.net/gallery/1 08378101/Dailies-Chicken-Farm-Tracking-App
- https://www.behance.net/gallery/1 08535915/Eja/modules/621934371